<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Specifications on CRM Portal Interface</title>
    <link>https://electrumpayments.github.io/crmportal-interface-docs/specification/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Specifications on CRM Portal Interface</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the Apache 2.0 license</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://electrumpayments.github.io/crmportal-interface-docs/specification/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Definitions</title>
      <link>https://electrumpayments.github.io/crmportal-interface-docs/specification/definitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrumpayments.github.io/crmportal-interface-docs/specification/definitions/</guid>
      <description>AirtimeDataPurchase Details of a airtime/data purchase  Name Type Required Default Restrictions Description   transactionId string required   Optional identifier for the transaction   msisdn string optional   The mobile number of the customer.   requestAmount integer required  format:int64 Amount in minor denomination, e.g. R799.95 is encoded as 79995   serviceProvider string required   The provider of the service.   purchaseDate string required  format:date-time Date of the purchase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://electrumpayments.github.io/crmportal-interface-docs/specification/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrumpayments.github.io/crmportal-interface-docs/specification/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Version 2.0.1
The Electrum CRM Portal Interface describes a server interface against which calls can be made to retrieve information from a backend CRM system. The intended use cases include the lookup of customer-linked account or purchase history data from a bank or retailer&amp;#x27;s CRM environment. It is not intended that the CRM system is hosted by Electrum, but rather that this interface abstracts the logic required to execute a set of predefined CRM queries, hence simplifying communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operations</title>
      <link>https://electrumpayments.github.io/crmportal-interface-docs/specification/operations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrumpayments.github.io/crmportal-interface-docs/specification/operations/</guid>
      <description> getPurchaseHistory Query purchase history
POST /crmportal/v2/purchaseHistory
Lookup a customer&amp;#x27;s purchase history for a specified service.
Security  httpBasic  Request Content-Type: application/json
Parameters  Name Located in Required Description Default Schema 
 body body yes A JSON body containing request parameters.  PurchaseHistoryRequest 

Response Content-Type: application/json
   Status Code Reason Response Model     200 An array of purchases matching the query. PurchaseHistoryResponse    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>https://electrumpayments.github.io/crmportal-interface-docs/specification/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrumpayments.github.io/crmportal-interface-docs/specification/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>This page describes changes to the CRM Portal Interface implemented for different releases of the interface.
v2.0.0 Released 22 March 2018
 Added missing set method in AirtimeDatePurchase class.  v2.0.0 Released 19 March 2018
 Not backwards compatible. Added BaseResponse class. PrepaidElectricityPurchase class now extends the BaseResponse class. Added a AirtimeDataPurchase class that extends the BaseResponse class. Added multiple tender support.  v1.0.1 Released 2 February 2017
 PurchaseHistoryRequest JSON body is required in post  v1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swagger</title>
      <link>https://electrumpayments.github.io/crmportal-interface-docs/specification/swagger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrumpayments.github.io/crmportal-interface-docs/specification/swagger/</guid>
      <description>The swagger (Open API) definition of the interface specification can be found here, as well as below.
Many tools are available for processing swagger files, and using a code generation tool to create a boilerplate client or server can be an excellent starting point for development. We highly recommend looking at swagger-codegen for a generator in your preferred language when starting out.
Swagger definition --- swagger: &amp;quot;2.0&amp;quot; info: description: &amp;quot;The Electrum CRM Portal Interface describes a server interface against\ \ which calls can be made to retrieve information from a backend\ \ CRM system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>